SARAH KIRBY.

Front-end Developer / Designer

m + 44 7562 781121

sk.irby@icloud.com

w sarahkirby.dev

github.com/sarahkirby

ABOUT

I'm Sarah, a hybrid Front-end Developer & Designer who has recently relocated to London from New Zealand. I have 2 + years experience working as a UI developer, using technology such as React, TypeScript and Sass. I'm looking for opportunities to build on my React experience where I can begin to explore the functional side of Javascript.

EXPERIENCE

♦ Front-end developer

Catalyst IT Limited

August 2017 - February 2019

- Theme developer for Learning Management Systems
- Designed and developed a reusable theme template that allowed for more streamlined project delivery
- Designed high fidelity prototypes that helped secure a £100,000 project
- · Worked across multiple teams as well as remotely for overseas offices
- Liaised with clients to understand their project requirements
- Implement solutions for cross-browser compatibility issues

♦ Front-end developer & Designer

enrichme

May 2016 - October 2018

- Responsible for creating the look and feel of enrichme along with building the user interface with React, Typescript and Sass
- Work alongside a UX designer to help understand our audience and how to best create a seamless experience for them
- Translate brief requirements into designs and work alongside fellow developers on implementation
- Produce high fidelity mock-ups from wireframes

Design Tutor

Wellington Institute of Technology

September 2017 - December 2017

- Introduce students to design principles and software in a 17 week
 Certificate in Creativity course
- Able to present, communicate, and teach design and creative methodologies to new students
- Re-designed existing teaching resources to improve learning outcomes for students

EDUCATION

Diploma of Web Development

July 2015 - May 2016 ACG Yoobee School of Design

Bachelor of Creative Technologies (Digital Media)

March 2012 - November 2014 Wellington Institute of Technology

TECHNICAL

Front-end

CSS Sass LESS Bootstrap JQuery

Responsive UI Javascript React Git

Theme development Command line

Design

Web design Illustrator Photoshop
InDesign UXPin

ENJOYS

Web development, UI animations, Web design, User Experience, React, Learning, Sustainability, Travel, Outdoor Adventures, Biking.

REFEREES

Nikki Sinclair

Senior Consultant, Catalyst IT Limited

• Wellington, New Zealand

Tomas van Ammers

enrichme co-founder

Wellington, New Zealand

Contact details available on request.